https://vigilantinc.com/about/privacy-policy.php

Vigilant Inc.,
Learn
Why Vigilant?
Wine Racks & Wine Cellars
Why Vigilant Wine Racks?
Refrigerated Wine Cabinets
Why Vigilant Wine Cabinets & Lockers?
Wine Cellar Doors
Why Vigilant Doors?
Cigar Humidors
Why Vigilant Cigar Humidors?
Learn
Why Vigilant?
Wine Racks & Wine Cellars
Why Vigilant Wine Racks?
Refrigerated Wine Cabinets
Why Vigilant Wine Cabinets & Lockers?
Wine Cellar Doors
Why Vigilant Doors?
Cigar Humidors
Why Vigilant Cigar Humidors?
The Importance of Privacy
At Vigilant, Inc. we take the protection of your personal privacy seriously. Although we collect information from you, we maintain the integrity of that information and do not share or sell it with any third party organization.
Conditions of Use
The Vigilant website has been made available to you subject to your compliance with the terms and conditions set forth below (the "Conditions of Use"). Please read this document carefully before accessing or using the website. By accessing or using this website, you are agreeing to be bound by the Conditions of Use. If you do not wish to be bound by the Conditions of Use, you should not access or use the website.
Read full disclosure on Vigilant, Inc. conditions of use
If you have any questions about this policy, please feel free to contact us at:
Vigilant Inc.
85 Industrial Park Drive
Dover, NH 03820 USA
Toll-free: 888.812.4427 (U.S. Only)
Local: 603.285.0400
Fax: +1.603.285.0420
Email: info@vigilantinc.com
How We Use Your Information
Like most companies on the web, we automatically track general personal information for the purpose of establishing or enhancing our relationship with our users. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us improve the content, design, and layout of the site. When you visit Vigilantinc.com, our web server gathers this information by tracking your domain name (e.g. aol.com) or IP address, not your e-mail address.
Communication
We use your collected information to provide you with customer support, process transactions, respond to requests, send newsletters with updates and special offers, advertisements, seeking your feedback, and connect you to our website (vigilantinc.com).
When you place an order or fill out a form, we need your name and e-mail address, which we use to fulfill your order and deliver information to your regarding your order. To process, fulfill, and service your request, we also need a mailing address, credit card number, and credit card expiration date. Your credit card information is kept strictly private and confidential.
Optimization
We utilize user information, behavioral metrics, and other non-personally identifiable information to operate, provide, improve, and maintain our website. We also use it to develop new products and services, to prevent abuse and fraud, to personalize advertisements, and for administrative and internal business purposes.
Advertising
We collect use information, including personal information, behavioral metrics, geo-location data, demographic data and marketing preferences to personalize and display advertisements.
Protecting Your Privacy
Whenever you place an order, you automatically use Vigilant's secure e-commerce server and secure server software (SSL). This means that all the information you input is encrypted before it is sent to us, and once submitted, all customer data is protected against unauthorized access.
If you supply us with your telephone or fax number, you may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders you have placed online or your online user account. We will contact you by phone on an as needed basis. Your phone number will not be used for solicitations.
To learn more about staying safe and secure online visit Google's Safety Center
Use of "Cookies"
Like most e-commerce and membership sites, we use cookies to collect information, which are small bits of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personal information, but they do remember your settings and the last time you visited.
What is a cookie?
Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your device when you visit a website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognizes that cookie. Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognize a user's device. You can find more information about cookies at: allaboutcookies.org.
Cookies serve many purposes, like remembering your preferences, letting you navigate between pages efficiently, and generally improve your overall web experience. They can also help ensure that advertisements you see online are more relevant to your interests.
Performance Cookies
Vigilant collects cookies to capture information about page visits (e.g. "performance cookies"). This information is anonymous and Vigilant uses it only internally to deliver the most pertinent content to our visitors. Information from the cookie is used to gauge page popularity, analyze traffic patterns on our website and guide website development improvements.
Targeting and Functionality Cookies
In our email broadcasts, Vigilant tracks usage statistics (e.g. "targeting and functionality cookies"). We track e-mail "opens" – meaning we track who opens our e-mail messages and when you open it. We also track "clicks" via encoded URLs. This indicates that we track if you click on the links contained in our e-mail messages. This information is used internally only to help us deliver relevant messaging, and is not shared with any third parties.
Also, as part of our marketing efforts, Vigilant uses Google AdWords Re-marketing services which is a Behavioral Targeting process provided by Google. It connects the activity of visitors on vigilantinc.com with the Adwords advertising network and the Doubleclick Cookie to enable us to serve you more pertinent advertisements. You can opt out of the cookie tracking here:
http://google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en
Understand what information is collected by Google in their Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. – Find their
Privacy Policy
Necessary Cookies
Vigilant does not require that you accept cookies and/or you may withdraw your consent to our use of cookies at any time by adjusting your browser's privacy settings, however, some functionality on our website such as the online store check-out process, and web forms functionality and submissions may be disabled if you decline to accept cookies ( e.g. "necessary cookies").
Opting Out of Cookies
You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it but remember functionality of our website may not work as expected.
Analytics Tools
We use analytics tools and other third party technologies, such as Google Analytics and DoubleClick Cookies, to collect non-personal information in the form of various usage and user metrics when you use our online website. These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior and usage information, feature use metrics and statistics, usage and purchase history, MAC Address, mobile unique device ID, and other similar information.
The third party analytics companies who collect information on our website and other online products and/or services may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your activities across their network of websites as well as online and/or mobile products and services. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies.
In addition to our use of technologies as described herein, we may permit certain third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to you based on your use of our website to collect and use data about your use of our website. For more information about this practice, please see the "Third Party Disclosures" section below.
You may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or you may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page.
Google has additional information available about their Re-marketing Privacy Guidelines, Policies, and Restrictions.
Third Party Disclosures
Vigilant, Inc. uses your personal information for the purposes of serving you to the best of our ability. Occasionally we may share or make available aggregate customer information to third parties. For instance, we may share non-individual statistical or demographic information in aggregate form with third parties. If you do not want us to share your personal information with other companies or organizations, let us know by e-mailing us at info@vigilantinc.com.
Finally, you understand that we must cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer.
Consent of Use
By using our web site, you are consenting to the collection and use of information provided and collected by Vigilant, Inc.
Delivery Policy
Vigilant uses several different carriers for our products depending on size, weight and customer choice. For more information on any of our shipping practices, please visit our
shipping and returns page.
Web Security and Encryption
Vigilant uses state-of-the-art online encryption and site security software and practices to ensure that our customer's data and transactions are fully secure. Our website is guaranteed to be hacker safe and is 128 SSL secure. Your credit card data is never stored. If you have additional questions in regards to our website security, please e-mail us at info@vigilantinc.com.
Return and Refund Policies
Vigilant guarantees your product for a period of 30 days. After the initial 30 days our 2 year product warranty takes over. For more information on these or any of our return and refund policies, please review our product guarantees.
Send Us Feedback
If you have questions, comments, or ideas regarding our privacy practices, please e-mail us at info@vigilantinc.com.
Subscription Manager
Vigilant maintains a strict communications policy with our customers. Once we have established a business relationship with you, you are added to our e-mail distribution lists. We strictly adhere to all Can-SPAM policies and procedures. If you do not want to receive our e-mail messages, please contact us and we will remove you from our contact list.
Enduring Quality, Craftsmanship and Design
Why Vigilant?
Our Excellent BBB rating since 2006
"Best of Houzz" Awards
Our Products are Proudly Made in USA
© 2020 All Rights Reserved.
Vigilant Inc.|
85 Industrial Park Drive |
Dover,
